

# EZEQUIEL DEL VITTO

## CERTIFIED TRANSLATOR (EN<>SPA)

#### **ABOUT ME**

My name is Ezequiel and I am a Full Stack Developer. My stack involves HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, React, Mongo, Node.js and Express.

Besides, I am a Literary and Certified Translator with over 6 years of translation and proofreading experience. I can guarantee high-quality professional results.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML5 and CSS3
- Javascript
- React
- Mongo
- Node.js
- Express
- Git and GitHub

#### CONTACT

E-mail: delvittoezequiel@gmail.com Mobile number; (+54) 11-5802-2188 Residence: Buenos Aires, Argentina

### **JOB EXPERIENCE**

### CERTIFIED TRANSLATIONS | FREELANCER

NOV 2018 - PRESENT

- Translation of official documents
- Translation of academic documents
- Subtitling
- Proofreading

#### **PRIVATE ENGLISH TEACHER**

APRIL 2015 - DECEMBER 2020

- International exams preparation
- Essay composition
- Speaking and fluency

### **EDUCATION**

# COURSEIT - PROGRAMMING SCHOOL

NOVEMBER 2020 - SEPTEMBER 2021

- Frontend course
- Backend course

### UNIVERSIDAD DEL MUSEO SOCIAL ARGENTINO

MARCH 2012 - NOVEMBER 2018

- English Certified Translator (2012-2018)
- Certified Court Interpreter (2016 2018)
- Literary and non-literary translator (2012 - 2015)